swinburneonline.edu.au 2013-11-25

# Privacy

**We value your privacy**

Swinburne University of Technology acknowledges and respects the privacy of individuals. We advise that much of the information that you may have provided to, or may be asked to provide, to Swinburne University of Technology is 'personal information'. As a general rule, personal information is not released by Swinburne University of Technology to other organisations, except in response to legal requirements such as a subpoena, and information regarding an individual will not be disclosed to a third party without the individual's consent, except where the third party is directly acting as our agent. 

**Why do we collect your information**

This information is normally collected for the purposes of processing your application, registration or inquiry for a Swinburne University of Technology course, activity or interest group. Information that we collect will be used for keeping you informed of upcoming events, improving the student experience and assisting us in improving and marketing our services to you. For more information refer to the Privacy Collection Notice.

**Security**

Swinburne University uses and implements industry standards for the security and protection of information collected, and this information is securely stored and access is restricted to authorised personnel only, ensuring that your personal information is protected and safeguarded 

**Access to your information**

You have a right of access to, and alteration of personal information concerning yourself held by the University, in accordance with Government Legislation. 

**Privacy policy**

Swinburne University has a [Privacy Policy](http://policies.swinburne.edu.au/ppdonline/showdoc.aspx?recnum=POL/2008/166) that can be found on its Policies and Procedures Database, which outlines the ways in which we intends to meet our privacy commitments and details the procedures for making complaints under the Act. 

**Contact**

If staff have any queries in relation to privacy at Swinburne University of Technology, please contact Swinburne Legal.
